Guide to the Gwathmey Siegel & Associates Architects, LLC, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project Records, 1965-2010
  - Apt 25 CPS, 2004
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1843)
  - Villa Jumeira
    Job number: 20-0104
    Job location: Dubai, United Arab Emirates
    Client: Dubai ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 1611)
    - Correspondence (Box 1611)
    - Specifications (Box 1611)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 1611, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1851–1852)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1611, Box 1851–1852, Box 1854, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1853)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1854)
  - Glenstone: Residence, 2006
    Job number: 20-0206
    Job location: Outside Washington D.C.
    Client: Potomac, MD ANONYMOUS
    - Correspondence (Box 1841)
    - Specifications (Box 1841)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1841, Box 1862–1863)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1841, Box 1861, Box 1864, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1864)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1864–1868)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1869)
  - Glenstone: Farm Tenant House (Artist Studio), 2006
    Job number: 20-0211
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1881)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1881–1882)
  - Glenstone: Residence + Studio (Museum), 2006
    Job number: 20-0212
    Client: Poromac, MD ANONYMOUS
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1891)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1891–1898)
  - Glenstone: Poolhouse, 2006
    Job number: 20-0311
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1901)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1901)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1901)
  - Design Study for World Trade Center Site
    Job number: 20-0209
    Client: World Trade Center
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1911, Box 2076)
  - W Hoboken
    Job number: 20-0312
    Job location: Hoboken, NJ
    Project type: Mixed Use Development
    Client: W Hotels
    - Background and Reports (Box 1921)
    - Design Development (Box 1921)
    - Correspondence (Box 1921)
    - Specifications (Box 1921)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 1921)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1922–1924)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1921)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1925–1938)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1939)
  - 311 W. Broadway (SoHo Mews)
    Job number: 20-0418
    Client: 311 W. Broadway (SoHo Mews)
    - Background and Reports (Box 1941)
    - Design Development (Box 1941)
    - Correspondence (Box 1941)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1941–1942, Box 1944)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1941, Box 1943–1944)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1945–1947)
  - W Downtown, 123 Washington
    Job number: 20-0504
    - Background and Reports (Box 1921)
    - Design Development (Box 1921)
    - Correspondence (Box 1921)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1952)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1921, Box 1951)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1953–1955)
  - Apartment 51/52 One Beacon Court
    Job number: 20-0512
    Client: 1 Beacon Ct ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 1611)
    - Correspondence (Box 1611)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1611, Box 1961)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1961–1963)
  - 34 Long Point Rd; Sag Harbor Residence
    Job number: 20-0514
    Job location: Sag Harbor, NY
    Client: Sag Harbor ANONYMOUS
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1971)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1792A, Box 1972–1973)
  - School of Architecture Renovation, History of Art Building and Arts Library, Yale, 2008
    Job number: 20-0515
    Job location: New Haven, CT
    Client: Yale University
    - Background and Reports (Box 1981, Box 1981A)
    - Design Development (Box 1981)
    - Correspondence (Box 1981)
    - Specifications (Box 1981–1982)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1984)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1981, Box 1983)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1981, Box 1985–1993)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1994–2004)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 1981, Box 2005–2006)
  - 400 5th Avenue (Setai)
    Job number: 20-0604
    Client: 400 5th Ave LLC (Setai)
    - Background and Reports (Box 1651)
    - Correspondence (Box 1651)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 2011)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1651, Box 2011)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 2012–2016)
  - Apartment 40/41, 2007
    Job number: 20-0605
    Client: Apt 40/41 ANONYMOUS
    - Correspondence (Box 1611)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 1611, Box 2021)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1611)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 2022–2023)
  - Villa St. Barths, 2010
    Job number: 20-0607
    Job location: Saint Barthélemy, French West Indies
    Client: St. Barthelemys ANONYMOUS
    - Correspondence (Box 1651)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2031)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 2031)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1651)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 2031)
  - Fifth Avenue Penthouse
    Job number: 20-0702
    Client: Fifth Avenue ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 1611)
    - Correspondence (Box 1611)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 2041)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1611)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 2043–2044)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 2042)
  - M-1 Apartment, 2009
    Job number: 20-0707
    Client: Fifth Avenue + Central Park ANONYMOUS
    - Correspondence (Box 1611)
    - Specifications (Box 1611)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 2051)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1611)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 2052–2053)
  - Windsor Digital Residence
    Job number: 20-0708
    Client: Windsor Digital
    - Correspondence (Box 1651)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1651, Box 2061)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 2061–2063)